studyspanish.com 2019-03-11

# Privacy Policy - StudySpanish.com

> Our most important asset is our relationship with you, and we want you to feel comfortable and secure when using our Website. Please be assured that we are serious about the protection of your personal information.

StudySpanish.com (“ **we** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”) values your privacy and is committed to protecting and securing your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how and when StudySpanish.com collects, uses and shares your information when you use our Services. This Privacy Policy applies to our website StudySpanish.com (the “ **Site** ”).

 **By using our and/or purchasing a Membership you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country you reside in or supply information from, you authorize StudySpanish.com to use your information in the United States and any other country where StudySpanish.com operates as described herein. Accordingly, please be sure to read this Privacy Policy before using the Services or submitting information to us.**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@studyspanish.com.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

The information we collect from you enables us to fulfill your requests for our services (such as purchasing a site membership, or ordering the audio course); send you information or content we believe may be of interest to you; and keep you aware of any updates to our Site and your Membership. We will never intentionally share this information with any outside entity, except as described below in the section, “Information Sharing and Disclosure”.

##### Information Collected Upon Registration

You may browse our Site without registering. However, if you would like to place an order or become a member, then you must complete the account registration process and become a member on our Site. When you create, register, or edit your free StudySpanish.com account, you provide some basic personal information, such as your name, email address, and password. When you purchase our products or services (such as Premium Membership, or Camino del Éxito), you must provide us with your credit card, debit card, or other type of acceptable payment information along with your billing and shipping address information. You are not required to provide us this information, however, without it we will not be able to process your order.

##### SUPPLEMENTATION OF TEACHER INFORMATION

If you register as a teacher, we collect various information such as email, name, school name and address and phone number. We collect this information so that we can confirm that you actually are a teacher.

Sometimes we offer educational discounts to bonafide Spanish teachers. In order to qualify teachers for educational discounts, we may call or email the teacher’s employer for the purpose of verifying the teacher’s credentials as a Spanish teacher.

##### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY

###### COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer by a website. Cookies contain information that can be read by a web server to help identify you and your activities on our website. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

Like many sites, we also use cookies. When you log on to our site, we use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site by allowing you to move from page to page without having to log on again on each page. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do you may not be able to log on or use all of the features of this website.

###### SITE USE LOGGING

Our servers automatically record information created by your use of the Site or our Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, and web page visited.

###### SITE ANALYTICS AND SITE ADS

We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics and a third-party advertising service called Google AdSense. Google is firmly committed to the privacy of their advertisers and users. While Google does use cookies, Google does not associate a user’s search activity with his/her ad click history.

#### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

We do not disclose your private personal information except in the limited circumstances described here.

###### PURCHASES

In order to process an online order for a product or service on StudySpanish.com, we use a reputable third party processing service, Stripe ([www.stripe.com](http://www.stripe.com/)). Stripe is provided with your name, address, email and credit card information, in order to process the charge and verify that it is not fraudulent. All communication with Stripe from StudySpanish.com is encrypted and secure.

###### EMAIL MARKETING

We engage an email marketing service, MailChimp (www.mailchimp.com), in order to send you emails periodically. We provide the email marketing service with your email address, first and last name, and the type of membership you have. If you chose to not receive email newsletters, then your information if removed from MailChimp and will not be used for email marketing.

Emails are only sent to you if you have chosen to ‘Receive Newsletters’ when you registered for an account. You can change this setting by going to your account profile, or by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in any of the marketing emails that you received.

###### BUSINESS TRANSFERS

In the event that StudySpanish.com is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

#### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We are make our best effort to protect all information we receive from you. No computer system is entirely secure, but we have implemented measures that reduce the likelihood of a security breach.

We implement technologies and practices such as password protection, encryption, SSL, firewalls, data access restrictions to prevent any loss, theft or misuse of data.

All payment information (credit card, debit card) is encrypted when transported from your browser to our servers.  Once that information has been provided to the merchant service (Stripe) for processing (also using SSL), we only store the last four digits of the credit/debit card, and the expiration date.  We do not have access to your credit/debit card information after the payment has been processed.

#### ACCOUNT CANCELLATION

You may cancel your StudySpanish.com account at any time. Just login to your account and go to “My Account”, then click on the “Cancel Membership” link. Under normal circumstances your account will be deleted immediately. If you need assistance cancelling your account, send an email to webmaster@studyspanish.com from the email address that the account is registered to.

#### SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENTS

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if your account is about to expire due to inactivity, we will send you a warning prior to deleting your records. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option of deactivating your account.

#### LEGAL DISCLAIMER

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

#### CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

  * Print Page
  * Email Page
